<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home Page on LCASTOR website</title><link>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/</link><description>Recent content in Home Page on LCASTOR website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 15:51:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Software</title><link>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/software/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/software/</guid><description>Software The software components developed in-house by the LCAS members of the team are:
Topological navigation People detection and tracking Engagement detection Gesture Recognition Decision Marking and planning Behaviour specification and planning Door opening Failure notification and recovery The followings are the third-party software that we deploy on the robot:
Metric navigation: move_base Object detection: YOLOv3 OCR: Keras-OCR Human pose detection: OpenPose Manipulation and grasping: MoveIt! Dialogue management: Rasa Speech recognition: Google Cloud Speech API</description></item><item><title>Robots</title><link>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/robots/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/robots/</guid><description>Robots TIAGo Pepper Lindsey/Linda</description></item><item><title>Competitions</title><link>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/competitions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/competitions/</guid><description>Competitions Participation RoboCup 2018 - Montreal, Canada. June 16-22, 2018. SPQReL team Robocup@HOME SPL - including Marc Hanheide and Francesco Del Duchetto.
RoboCup 2017 - Nagoya, Japan. July 27-31, 2017. SPQReL team Robocup@HOME SPL - including Marc Hanheide.
Qualified 3rd place!!! Competitions Organised The PUB.R Competition - ICRA 2023, London, United Kingdom. The Preparation and dish Up of an English Breakfast with Robots The default platforms provided are the TIAGo robots (the same we use for the RoboCup@HOME competitions).</description></item><item><title>Scientific Objectives</title><link>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/scientific-objectives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 16:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/scientific-objectives/</guid><description>Scientific Objectives We present the main scientific contributions achieved by the research group and the research topics relevant to the RoboCup@Home competitions and outline how they will contribute and be further developed in this context.
Planning and plan execution The deployment of robots in populated environments interacting with non-expert users requires facing many sources of uncertainty during task execution such as incomplete information about the environment or unpredictable behaviours coming from humans.</description></item><item><title>Members</title><link>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/members/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://francescodelduchetto.github.io/LincolnRobocupWebsite/members/</guid><description>Team Members Team Leader Francesco Del Duchetto Team Members Riccardo Polvara Leonardo Guevara Matthew Story Karoline Heiwolt Jacob Swindell Nikolaus Wagner Alex Elias Luca Castri Advisory Board Marc Hanheide</description></item></channel></rss>